Toggle navigation

Privacy Policy
==============

1. This website (the “Site”) is owned and operated by Saga Communications, Inc. and/or one of its affiliated companies (collectively “Saga”). Saga has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to user privacy and online data security, and to communicate its online information gathering, use and dissemination practices for users of this Site. We encourage users to take time to read and understand this Privacy Policy, and to contact us if you have any questions or concerns with this Privacy Policy or anything you see or experience on this Site.
2. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the “Terms of Use” for this Site. This Privacy Policy will fully disclose our policy about the collection, maintenance, use, disclosure, and security of personally identifiable information obtained from users of the Site. By personally identifiable information, we mean a user’s name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, financial information or any other information that can be used to contact an individual, or which is identifiable of a specific individual (“Identifiable Information”).
3. Saga shall use your Identifiable Information only in association with its operation and administration of the Site and its communications with you. Saga shall maintain the confidentiality of your Identifiable Information in the same manner in which it protects its own confidential information of like kind, but in no event shall Saga take less than reasonable precautions to prevent the unauthorized disclosure or use of your Identifiable Information.
4. Saga may disclose your Identifiable Information to its employees and contractors on a need to know basis provided that such employees and contractors have confidentiality obligations to Saga. Saga may also disclose your Identifiable Information as required by applicable law or pursuant to a subpoena, order and/or request of a court or other governmental, legislative or regulatory body. Lastly, Saga may modify your Identifiable Information such that it is not identifiable as yours, and Saga may store, analyze, manipulate, aggregate, display, disclose, distribute, retain and otherwise use such unidentifiable information without restriction.
5. Saga’s obligations under this Privacy Policy do not apply to any information or data that:
    1. is not identifiable as yours;
    2. is or becomes entirely in the public domain;
    3. was known to Saga prior to its access to the information or data;
    4. received lawfully from a third party through no breach of any obligation of confidentiality owed to you; and/or
    5. created by Saga independently of its access to or use of your Identifiable Information.
6. You have the option to opt out of receiving information from Saga. Saga will not provide your Identifiable Information to its sponsors, advertisers, affiliates and/or strategic partners, unless you are selected as a contest winner and disclosure of your Identifiable Information is required for the pick-up or use of your prize. You may also opt out of receiving information from Saga by sending an e-mail with your request to [interactive@sagacom.com](http://sagacommunications.com/pages/10199370.php).
7. You may review, update and correct your Identifiable Information by editing your User Profile. To edit your User Profile, visit the website and choose login from the club menu in the main navigation.. To have your Identifiable Information returned you can send an e-mail request to [interactive@sagacom.com](http://sagacommunications.com/pages/10199370.php).
8. Subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy, Saga will return your Identifiable Information, and all copies thereof, within a reasonable time after your request. However, Saga may retain one (1) copy of all of your Identifiable Information solely for its own record keeping purposes. Saga will have no obligation or responsibility to return or provide any unidentifiable information to you.
9. The security of this Site, and of the servers and other computer equipment used to bring you this Site, is a high priority of Saga. We maintain this Site and all associated data with technical, administrative, and physical safeguards to protect against loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification, and improper disclosure. We follow industry-proven security procedures such as encrypted administrative communication, restricted access to underlying machines, and firewalls at network access points. No computer system or information can ever be fully protected against every possible hazard, but Saga is committed to providing reasonable and appropriate security controls to protect this Site and its information against foreseeable hazards.
10. Saga’s servers will collect certain technical information from your computer when you access or use this Site. Below we have summarized this technical information:
    1. Internet Protocol Addresses. Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses are identification numbers assigned to a user’s computer by its Internet Service Provider each time the user logs onto the Internet, or are permanently assigned if a user has an open connection to the Internet.
    2. Web Logs. Saga maintains standard web logs that record basic information about visitors to this Site. Our web logs contain the following information:
        1. The type of browser you are using when you access this Site, for example, Microsoft Edge, Google Chrome, etc.;
        2. The type of operating system you use, for example, Windows 10;
        3. The internet domain from which you access this Site and/or the address of the website you linked here from; and
        4. The date(s) and time(s) you visited this Site, and the pages you viewed and/or functions you used while you were at this Site.
    3. Use of IP Addresses and Web Log Information. Saga does not try to identify individuals or otherwise collect Identifiable Information from IP addresses or web log information. IP addresses and web log information are used by Saga to, among other things, administer the Site, help diagnose technical problems, to track and analyze aggregate data associated with the Site, to design this Site and identify popular features. Saga may aggregate IP addresses and/or web log information, and may store, analyze, manipulate, display, disclose, distribute, retain and otherwise use such unidentifiable information. We may also provide IP addresses and/or web log information to law enforcement agencies if someone tries to damage this Site or use it in an unauthorized or illegal way.
11. On the Internet, a cookie is a piece of information that a website transfers to a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. Saga does use cookies and cookies may be placed on your computer as a result of your use of this Site.
12. Questions, comments or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy and/or this Site should be directed to Saga’s Privacy Administrator by e-mailing such questions, comments or complaints to “[interactive@sagacom.com](http://sagacommunications.com/pages/10199370.php).”
13. Saga reserves the right to change the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy at any time in its sole discretion. Saga will provide notification of any change by posting the change on this Site. You are responsible for regularly reviewing this Privacy Policy and all such changes. Continued use of the Site after any such changes have been posted shall constitute your agreement to such changes.

© Copyright 2024 Saga Communications, Inc. · All rights reserved.
